saralrozgar.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Jobs in India | Saral Rozgar

Company is committed to protecting your privacy. 

**Collecting Your Personal Information**  
Company will ask you when Company need information that personally identifies you or allows Company to contact you. The personal information Company collect may include information about. The personal information Company collect includes your name, title, company or organization name, work E-mail, work phone, work or home address, information about your job function, information about your company, and credit card information. 

**Use of Your Personal Information**  
The personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized. 

In support of these uses, Company may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related Company products or services, and to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Site to your particular preference or interests. 

Company may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Company and our family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Company employees or agents, users of Company products or services, or members of the public. 

Personal information collected on the Site may be stored and processed in the India or any other country in which Company or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

**Control of Your Personal Information**  
Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of Company and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission – 

Please be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to Company in the context of other, separately operated, Company products or services. 

**Be safe**  
Regrettably, from time to time, false job postings are listed online and used to illegally collect personal information from unsuspecting job seekers. The placement of such false job postings is a violation of the [Terms of Use](http://www.saralrozgar.com/saralrozgar/terms-of-use) and may also be a criminal violation of federal and/or state law. 

Saral Rozgar™ is dedicated to stopping this abuse and providing the safest possible environment for you to search and apply to jobs and manage your career. 

Here are some important tips to use when dealing with prospective employers 

Do not give your social security number unless you are confident that the other party is who they claim to be. For example, you could ask them for a call-back number to use for verification purposes. 

Be careful when providing credit card or bank information, or engaging in any monetary transactions. Be sure to verify the legitimacy of the employer with whom you are interacting. 

Do not provide any non-work-related personal information (e.g., Social Security Number, eye color, marital status, etc.) over the phone or online. 

Be cautious when dealing with contacts outside your own country 

Be wary of emails that offer an opportunity that involves acting as a go-between for money transfers. Disregard the email and DO NOT follow through with the employment offer being made.
